[static]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[clears throat]
[muffled talking]
[clicks tongue] We are now closer
than we have ever been.
We are now closer
than we have ever been to victory.
Some...
Some are already calling it
the greatest...
[clears throat] Some are already
calling it the greatest victory
in the history...
of mankind.
Some are calling it already...
We are closer
than we have ever been to victory.
Some are already calling it
the greatest victory
in the history of military campaigns.
Today. I can announce
that the so-called Western Forces
of Texas and California
have suffered a very great loss.
A very great defeat
at the hands of the fighting men and women
of the United States military.
The people of Texas
and California should know
that they will be welcomed back
to these United States
as soon as their illegal
secessionist government is deposed.
I can also confirm
that the Florida alliance
has failed in its attempt
to force the brave people of the Carolinas
into joining the insurrection.
Citizens of America.
we are now closer than ever
to a historic victory.
[camera shutter clicks]
As we eliminate
the final pockets of resistance.
God bless you all
and God Bless America.
[distant explosion]
[live music playing]
["Lovefingers" by Silver Apples playing]
[indistinct shouting]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[woman] Where's the water!
Where's the water!
We've been waiting two hours.
Stand back. Hey. just back up.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
[people chanting]
We want water! We want water!
I have a baby!
- We want water!
- [camera shutter clicks]
[indistinct shouting]
[Joel] Lee.
- [crowd continues chanting]
- [indistinct shouting]
[indistinct shouting]
No!
[indistinct shouting continues]
- [loud thud]
- [shouting intensifies]
- [woman] You all right?
- We want water!
- [thudding]
- [grunting]
[woman] Help!
[woman screams]
[Lee] Here. here.
- You okay?
- [breathing heavily]
- Oh. fuck.
- What?
What? You're Lee Smith?
[breathes heavily. chuckles]
This is crazy.
Take this.
Oh. no. I. I can't take that.
Take it and put it on.
- [shouting continues]
- [helicopter hovers in distance]
Thank you so much.
- [man] Run!
- [Lee] Shit!
[shouting. screaming]
[inaudible]
[camera shutter clicks]
We woke up in Des Moines. lowa
- and he's wearing my wedding ring.
- [laughter]
- Yeah!
- There you go.
That's for you.
I made it for you. Yeah!
[indistinct chatter. shouting]
Jesus. The WiFi is fucking slow.
The word I'm getting. it's July 4th.
"The word you're getting."
Like everyone in this room
hasn't already heard this bullshit.
July 4th. Sammy.
The optics are irresistible.
The Western Forces
are stopped 120 miles from D.C.
The Florida Alliance
aren't far south of that.
The WF weren't stopped. They're stalled.
They lost their supply lines.
But it's the Race to Berlin.
There's no coordination
between the secessionists.
You watch.
As soon as D.C. falls.
they'll turn on each other.
[lighter flicks]
[electricity buzzes]
- [lighter flicks]
- [Lee] Really?
[Sammy] It's every night this week.
- Ugh.
- [Sammy] They'll switch to the generator.
Upload was almost done.
So. where you kids headed tomorrow?
Staying in New York a while
or venturing out?
Fuck you.
[chuckles]
Come on. Joel.
- So you can beat us there?
- I couldn't beat you in a brisk walk.
We're going to...
We're going to D.C.. Sammy.
Tomorrow morning. first thing.
Yeah. frontline. I figured.
No. no. not the frontline.
D.C.
[glass thuds]
What?
I'm gonna photograph the president.
Joel's gonna interview him.
Photograph and interview the president?
In D.C.?
That's the idea.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Are you serious?
[scoffs]
They shoot journalists
on site in the capital.
They literally see us as enemy combatants.
Not a single interview in 14 months.
And how are you gonna do this?
We get there before anyone else does.
You think there's a rush
to get executed on the South Lawn?
Sammy. July 4th. July 10th.
West Coast Forces.
fuckin'... Portland Maoists.
it's all the same.
D.C. is falling and the president
is dead inside the month.
Interviewing him is the only story left.
It's not a story if it never gets filed.
Lee. can I please
talk you out of this bullshit?
What do you think
the route's gonna be like?
There's nothing direct.
The interstates are vaporized.
And you can't get anywhere near Philly.
So you gotta go west.
maybe as far as Pittsburgh.
Then circle in from West Virginia.
You already had that route
all figured out. huh. Sammy?
Yeah. okay. I was kind of looking
to get down there myself.
- [exhales] Knew it.
- Not D.C.
I don't want a piece of your suicide pact.
I want Charlottesville. the frontline.
- Sammy.
- [Sammy] Hear me out.
Just 'cause I'm a rival news outlet...
[Joel] You're not a fucking rival.
You think I care if you fight
with whatever's left
of The New York Times?
You're worried I'm too old.
Can't move quick enough.
Aren't you?
Sure. Yes.
But...
you're gonna make me explain
why I have to be there?
If it's the frontline you want.
half the press in this room
are gonna be heading there
within 24 hours.
You want me to walk around
this fucking room begging for a ride?
[exhales]
I'm gonna finish the upload upstairs
and pass out.
Hopefully. it'll be time
by the time I wake up. [sighs]
My vote.
if Sammy wants a ride. I'm good with it.
You two figure it out.
Thank you. Lee.
[inhales] Yeah. thank you. Lee.
Make me the bad guy.
Ma'am. just a warning.
if you take the elevator.
we do sometimes have power cuts
which might mean a delay in your journey.
A delay?
We offer the option to use the stairs.
I'm on the tenth floor.
Your choice. ma'am.
[sighs]
[Jessie] Miss Smith?
Hey. it's me.
Do-- do you remember me from earlier?
Yeah. How did you know I was staying...
Yeah. I didn't mean to. like. stalk.
but. um. I know a lot of the press
use this hotel.
And. um. I wanted to say thanks.
And I want to give you this back.
Oh. no. It's okay. keep it.
- But I'm sure--
- Keep it. And buy a helmet.
And some Kevlar. okay. if you're planning
on attending more stuff like that.
I am. yeah. going to.
I'm-- I'm a photographer
and I wanna be
a war photographer. actually.
Um. by the way. you have
the same name as my hero.
Lee Miller.
She was one of the first
photojournalists into Dachau.
- Do you know her stuff?
- Yeah. I know who Lee Miller is.
Of course.
But I want to say
that you're also one of my heroes.
And you've got
the same name too. [chuckles]
Well. thank you. I'm in good company.
- What's your name?
- Jessie.
Jessie Collin.
So. Jessie. I've gotta walk up
ten flights of stairs.
But. if I ever see you again.
you better be wearing Kevlar
and that fluorescent.
You bet.
[soft music playing]
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music continues playing]
[exhales]
A word.
What the fuck is that girl doing here?
[Joel] Right. So. she came over
to the table last night
after you went to bed.
and we got talking and...
She's very cool and wanted to tag along.
So she's coming with us?
Lee. you let Sammy tag along.
You think he's gonna do well
running for cover
with bullets flying over his head?
[Lee] She's a kid. did you notice that?
[Joel] She's. like. 23.
and she wants to do what we do.
She wants to do what you do.
We had to start one day.
Were you much older than she is now?
Whatever happens.
she goes no further than Charlottesville.
All right. Let's go.
["Rocket USA" by Suicide plays]
- [seat belt clicks]
- [engine starts]
["Rocket USA" playing]
You don't wanna miss this.
Mr. President. do you regret
any actions implemented
during your third term in office?
I'm not gonna softball him. Sammy.
In retrospect. Mr. President.
do you still think it was wise
to disband the FBI?
Passive-aggressive.
Sir. how is your policy evolving
in the use of air strikes
against American citizens?
[chuckles] Oh. yeah. Now we're talking.
Just be sure you get the words out
before the piano wire gets too tight.
There's a gas station up ahead.
Looks open.
We got over half a tank.
[birds chirping]
What do you think?
Any chance to refuel. we should take.
Okay.
[engine stops]
Help you. folks?
Just looking for gas.
Y'all have a fuel permit?
No. we're...
We're actually just passing through.
Can't help you. sorry.
Sir. if we pay...
I was never gonna give it free.
Over the odds.
What's over the odds?
Three hundred
for half a tank and two cans.
[chuckles]
Three hundred buys you a sandwich.
We got ham or cheese.
Three hundred Canadian.
Okay.
Hey. Stretching your legs?
Uh. no. I just saw something
from the road.
This isn't going to take long.
Sure.
Are we good?
Yeah. we're good.
[birds chirping]
[man] Go ahead. check it out. Come on.
[water dripping]
[gasps]
I told her...
I don't mind if she looks.
Who are they?
Looters.
[weakly] I got kids. man. [coughs]
I actually know that guy.
Went to high school together.
He didn't talk to me much.
Much more talkative now.
We've been debating
what to do with them for two days now.
We go around in circles.
- [chuckles]
- [coughs]
[gasps]
Tell you what.
Why don't you put us and them
out of our misery and make a call?
I'll put rounds in them right now.
Or we'll beat 'em up a little more.
Strap them to the front.
We'll let them go after a couple of days.
[breathing heavily]
[strained breathing]
[chuckles]
Flip a coin if you like.
Would you stand with them?
- Stand with them?
- Yeah.
I'd like to take your picture.
Okay. Just stand over there?
Yeah.
Where do you want me?
Uh. between the two.
Got you.
I didn't take a photo.
I didn't take a single photo.
I didn't even remember a camera's on me.
Like. oh. my God. like. like.
why didn't I just tell him
not to shoot them?
- They're probably gonna kill them anyway.
- How do you know?
He doesn't know.
but that's besides the point.
Once you start asking yourself
those questions. you can't stop.
So we don't ask.
We record so other people ask.
Wanna be a journalist? That's the job.
- Hey. Lee.
- What?
Back off.
What am I saying that's wrong?
I'm not saying it's wrong.
she's just shook up.
Lee doesn't understand "shook up".
Whoa.
I'm not being protective of her?
You're the idiot who let her in this car.
What happened back there
is nothing in comparison
to what we're heading into.
You need to understand...
Oh. shit. she's crying.
The back seat is both a kindergarten
and an old people's home.
How did this happen?
Lee. what the fuck?
Lee's right.
I won't make that mistake again.
[president on radio] ...the terms
of the so-called peace summit
could only be rejected. truly rejected
by all great-thinking Americans.
To the secessionists. I say only this.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America.
We stand ready to fulfill
the promise of our forefathers.
to the flag. to the nation.
and to God.
Stop here a minute.
This seem like a good place
for a toilet break?
Just pull in.
[seat belt clicks]
Come with me.
[car door opens]
- Come with me.
- [sighs]
[tense music playing]
Shoot it.
Shoot the helicopter?
Yeah.
It's gonna make a good image.
[camera shutter clicking]
FE2s.
You don't see them around much.
Yeah.
They're my dad's cameras actually.
Don't worry. he's not dead.
He's...
sitting on his farm in Missouri.
pretending like none of this is happening.
[camera shutter clicks]
Lee.
I'm sorry for jamming my way
into your ride. okay?
I know you're really angry about it.
and I know you think
I don't know shit. but...
I'm not angry about that. Jessie.
I don't care what you do or don't know.
Okay. but you are angry with me.
There is no version of this
that isn't a mistake.
I know. because I'm it.
Joel and Sammy are it.
- It's my choice.
- Right.
And I'll remember that
when you lose your shit.
or you get blown up or shot.
[Jessie] Would you photograph
that moment if I got shot?
[Lee] What do you think?
[distant gunfire]
[distant explosion]
Every time I survived a war zone.
and got the photo.
I thought I was sending a warning home.
"Don't do this."
But here we are.
So it's existential.
What is?
What's eating you.
Don't worry about me. Sammy.
Am I allowed to say
I remember you at her age?
And I wasn't so different?
You weren't so different.
You think you're being hard on her.
and I think you're being hard on yourself.
- Okay. writer.
- Damn it. Lee. Stop.
I'm speaking truth.
And for the record. sure.
I'm worried about that girl.
And I'm worried about you too.
[Joel] What are you worrying
about Lee for?
Lee's lost her faith
in the power of journalism.
State of the nation is QED.
I can't answer to that. Sammy.
But I can tell you.
this gunfire...
is getting me extremely fucking hard.
[distant gunfire continues]
Look at that shit light up the sky.
[Lee] It's not our story.
- Yeah.
- [distant explosion]
But you know. bang-bang.
We're not going
anywhere near that in the dark.
But sunup?
If they're still at it. we'll take a look.
[sniffs]
Cool.
[huffs smoke]
Thanks.
[bottle clinks]
[object clacks. thuds]
[drumming fingers]
Action tomorrow.
We're going down there?
Yeah.
But not you.
You're gonna... You're gonna hang back.
I don't wanna hang back.
Oh. you have to hang back.
I'm not hanging back.
You should see your face.
[Joel huffs smoke]
Stomach doing turns. Right.
You don't get a minute of sleep tonight.
My advice.
don't expect to sleep.
That way if you do. it's a...
it's a nice surprise.
You gonna sleep?
[inhales]
I got a little bit Ativan. [exhales]
Got plenty.
I can give you some if you like.
Uh. no. it's okay.
Or...
I can stay up with you.
Keep you company.
N-no. I...
I don't wanna be a burden or whatever.
Sure.
But seriously. if you do get
freaked out or something.
just wake me up.
It's not nice being scared alone.
Thanks. Joel.
You bet. darling.
[insects chirping]
[soft music playing]
[distant explosion and gunfire]
- Get down! I said go flank the building!
- [man screaming]
No! Fuck!
- [screams]
- Shit!
- [man 1] Mike. come on!
- [metal clanks]
[camera shutter clicking]
- [gunfire]
- [car alarm blaring]
[Mike] Get me the fuck
out of here! Fuck!
I said go flank the fucking building!
Got it.
[gunfire continues]
Do something!
Get ready to move.
- Prep the smoke.
- Get me the fuck out of here!
- Fuck!
- Smoke down!
- [screams]
- On the count of three.
- Three. two. one.
- [man 3] Cover mel!
[camera shutter clicking]
- [man 1] Watch now.
- [Mike yells] Fuck!
- Fuck!
- Shit!
- [man 4] Hey. man. you all right?
- [Mike] I'm gonna get hit!
- [man 3] Go get him.
- [man 1] Yeah!
Now. move it! You gotta move!
[camera shutter clicking]
Mike's down! You gotta get him!
Mike's down.
- Move back!
- [panting]
Move back!
[grunts]
[camera shutter clicking]
[Mike groaning]
[man 1] I got you. Hang in.
Stay with me.
[Mike continues groaning]
- [man 1] Fuck! Give me gauze.
- [groaning]
[Jessie panting]
[distant groans]
[groaning continues]
[man groaning. crying]
[man crying]
[man coughing. groaning]
I need help.
["'Say No Go" by De La Soul playing]
["Say No Go" playing]
[inaudible]
[Joel] Holy fucking shit!
What a fucking rush!
[indistinct chatter]
- You're press?
- [Joel] Yes. ma'am.
IDs.
Okay. Are you staying the night?
Yeah. just one.
Park over there.
There's a canteen where you can eat.
And no tents available.
Thanks. ma'am.
[children chattering]
[Joel] You're good.
[girl] Eight. nine. ten.
- [Lee] Hey. get in there.
- [Joel] I'm gonna show these kids...
- Check this out. Okay!
- [Lee laughs]
- [boy] One. two. three. four...
- [Joel] Eleven. twelve. thirteen...
- [kids clamor]
- [Joel laughs] Yeah.
Your turn. Sammy.
[boy chuckles] Hey. wait up.
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
- [Lee] Brought you something.
- [Jessie] Oh. thanks.
[Lee] Don't forget to eat.
[Jessie] Yeah. I'm starving.
I'll eat once I handle this.
- [clears throat]
- Developing negs on the road.
Yeah. I got myself
a pretty neat travel kit.
I'm impressed.
Wanna know the secret
of getting the developer just right?
[Lee] Hmm.
Body temperature.
- Smart.
- Thank you.
So. how about you tell me the story
of how you became a photojournalist?
You don't know?
I thought I was one of your heroes.
Uh... [chuckles]
Yeah. I do.
When you were in college.
you took the motherfucking legendary photo
of the Antifa massacre.
Then you became the youngest ever
Magnum photographer.
That would be my Wikipedia page.
But what's missing from it?
I don't know. A lot.
Well. that's gotta sit here
for ten minutes.
so you might as well expand a little.
What about your folks?
Well. actually they're on a farm too.
- Oh?
- Except. Colorado.
Also pretending this isn't happening.
[scoffs] No shit.
Hey. these are dry.
Should we check them out?
Sure.
Still need a phone
even though you can't get a signal.
[clicks]
I don't want you to see these. Um...
They're not even in focus.
Like... [chuckles]
Exposure is all wrong.
Just keep looking.
Figure the strike rate for keepers
is 30 to one.
[clicking]
It's a great photo. Jessie.
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
[camera shutter clicking]
[birds chirping]
[dog barks in distance]
Did we just drive through a time portal?
It's The Twilight Zone.
[dog barks]
[engine stops]
[doorbell dings]
Hey there. Welcome.
Feel free to look around.
Hey.
Out of interest. but...
are you guys aware there's like a...
pretty huge civil war going on
all across America.
Oh. sure. but we just try to stay out.
"Stay out"?
With what we see on the news.
seems like it's for the best.
Yeah.
Well. let me know
if you wanna try anything on.
Thanks.
- Lee.
- Mm?
[scoffs]
What?
You're so war-torn.
you can't try on a dress?
Jesus... [clears throat]
When you haven't seen yourself
in a mirror...
- Oh. my God. Shut the fuck up.
- ...in a few days.
Turn around. I wanna take your photo.
No.
Come on.
Yes.
[sighs]
You're gonna take the photo?
You told me not to rush.
Yeah. but there's a sweet spot.
and you're missing it.
Don't wanna miss your sweet spot.
- [chuckles]
- [camera clicks]
Well. no. that was not the moment.
[chuckles]
Okay.
One more.
- Lee.
- Yes.
You're pretty when you smile.
- [light chuckle]
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [whirs. clicks]
- There you go.
[Joel] Hey.
How about this?
Yeah. nice.
Not gonna take a picture?
Right.
You know what. though.
running a little low on film.
You're mean. I'm out.
[Jessie chuckles]
- [door opens]
- [doorbell dings]
I'm gonna go try this on.
[door closes]
[doorbell dings]
You actually bought something?
[Lee scoffs]
She did. She's paying now.
[inhales deeply]
It's so weird.
This place is like everything
I'd forgotten.
Funny. I was thinking it felt like
everything I remembered.
Look at the tops of the buildings.
Be subtle.
Wouldn't have suited us anyway. Lee.
We'd have gotten bored.
[Lee scoffs]
[president on radio] / remain ready
to accept the full immediate
and unconditional surrender
of the secessionist forces.
To liberate the people
of the subjugated states
and start rebuilding our great nation.
[Sammy] Enough of this shit.
- [clicks]
- Words might as well be random.
What do you think he'll actually say
if I do get a microphone over to him?
Not much.
The ones that get taken.
Gaddafi. Mussolini. Ceausescu.
they're always lesser men than you think.
At the end. they let you down. Joel.
Just as long as he isn't dead
before I get there.
Hold up.
[christmas music playing]
There was a turnoff
three or four miles back.
Maybe we should turn around.
take another route.
Can you see anything?
- No.
- [clicks]
[Joel] Nothing. no shapes.
no movement. nothing?
No.
Okay. I'm gonna drive forward a little.
[christmas music continues playing]
Should we keep going?
[gunshots]
Shit!
[tires screeching]
- [gunshot]
- [tires screeching]
[panting]
[breathes deeply]
Where you going?
- With them.
- Don't be such a hotshot.
Just keep your head down.
No shit.
I wouldn't try drivin' on.
This guy's a good shot.
[gunshots]
[breathing heavily]
Hey. [panting]
What's going on?
Someone in that house.
they're stuck.
We're stuck.
Who do you think they are?
Hmm.
No idea.
[breathing deeply]
Hey. We're press.
Cool.
Now I understand why it's written
on the side of your vehicle.
Are you WF? Who's givin' you orders?
[sighs] No one's giving us orders. man.
Someone's trying to Kill us.
We're trying to kill them.
You don't know
what side they're fighting for?
Oh. I get it.
You're retarded.
You don't understand a word I say.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- Yo! What's over there in that house?
[whirs. clicks]
Someone shooting.
Guys.
Shut the fuck up.
[christmas music continues playing]
[gunshot]
- [bullet shell clinks]
- [camera clicks]
[whirs]
I got good news.
[revs]
[birds chirping]
[taps Jessie]
Why don't you put your head down there?
Thanks. Sammy. I'm... good.
Take it from an old hand.
Sleep any chance you get.
You never know what's coming
around the next corner.
Yeah. all right.
[sighs]
- Sammy.
- What?
Got a car comin' up on us pretty fast.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Maybe they're just in a hurry.
[tires screech]
Oh. they're in a hurry. all right.
He smoked his tires on the last corner.
Okay. Well. we're not gonna
outrun anyone in this thing.
So slow down a little. Lee.
- Let 'em pass.
- Roger that.
[music playing loudly over speakers]
Don't look out at 'em.
They just roll on by.
[music playing loudly]
[honking]
Oh. shit. Here we go.
- [laughing]
- [continues honking]
What the fuck? Tony?
[panting]
- Fuck you!
- What the fuck?
How you guys doing?
You just scared the shit out of me.
Good. That was the idea.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I don't know. Joel.
What are you doing here?
- [Tony laughs]
- Fuck you! Fuck youl!
God. small world.
Small world. my ass.
They were following us.
Did you tell them
where we were headed back in New York?
Fuck. no.
Hey. Tony. did Joel tell you
where we were going back in New York?
I don't know. Lee. He was pretty drunk
when he was hitting on that girl
you got in the back seat.
- Oh. for...
- You're a dick.
Look. I must've been so wasted.
Lee. I'm done with Bohai.
He's lousy company.
He drives like a maniac.
[speaks Mandarin]
[laughs]
- Dude. what are you doing?
- I'm coming over to your car.
- [Lee] Tony!
- [Joel] Dude!
Are you fucking crazy. Tony?
- Just keep the car steady.
- No!
- Just keep it steady.
- Fuck!
- [Joel laughs]
- Don't worry. I've done this before.
What the fuck?
[Tony] Just keep the car steady. Lee.
[speaks Mandarin]
[Joel] Give me your hand.
- [Joel laughs]
- [Jessie grunts]
- [Sammy] You're out of your fucking mind.
- [Tony laughs]
- You crazy bastard.
- That was so fucking...
So fucking sick! [laughs]
I gotta do it.
What?
I'm doing it.
[Joel] Jesus. Lee.
Don't turn the wheel.
My new passenger.
Much better. much better.
- Pull over.
- Bye-bye. Tony.
Bye-bye. See you in Washington.
Fuck you!
[revving]
[laughing]
[music playing loudly]
I told you he drives like a maniac.
[continues laughing]
Where did they go?
This feel funny?
Where did your guy go. Tony?
He's just fucking around. that's all.
I don't want him fuckin' around.
I want Jessie back in this car.
Relax. Lee. He's just showing
how fast he can drive. The girl's fine.
How the fuck do you know if she's fine?
Can you see her?
- [horn blaring]
- Whoa!
[tires screeching]
- [Joel] Fuck!
- [grunts]
[brakes screech]
Oh. fuck.
[tires screeching]
[birds chirping]
Shit.
[inaudible]
[breathes heavily]
[sighs]
We need to go down there. Now.
If we go down there.
they're going to Kill us.
No.
Those aren't government forces.
Not up here.
We got our press passes. We're cool.
Those people do not wanna be seen
doing what they're doing.
Tell us. Lee.
[panting]
[sighs] They're talking.
They're probably just giving them a scare.
They killed all the people
in that fucking truck.
They could've killed the whole town.
but they'll stop now?
Who knows where those bodies are from?
Are the bodies in uniform?
No. they're not.
I'm going down.
- I'm coming with you.
- Me too.
I'm telling you every instinct in me says
this is death. okay? Death.
You stay. You stay ‘cause you're old
and you can't run.
Fuck it.
Shit.
Fuck this.
Who's doing the talking?
- [Joel] Me.
- Okay.
[man 1] Wyatt.
there's one hung up in there.
[Joel] Hey!
Hey. guys.
What's happening?
Guess there's... there's some kind
of misunderstanding here.
- [man 1] Yeah?
- [Joel] Yes. sir.
Those two guys over there.
they're my colleagues.
What kind of colleagues?
Journalists. sir.
We're actually just...
We're passing through.
Passing through to where?
Charlottesville.
Charlottesville?
What's in Charlottesville?
[exhales]
Good hiking.
I hear.
Actually. we are. uh...
No. we're covering. the. uh.
the university campus there.
[clears throat]
They started a new program.
They are reopening the school.
which is a... [sighs]
- surreal feel-good story.
- Mm-hmm.
And I... I guess we all need that.
Right?
Yeah.
- This guy is your colleague?
- Yeah.
- This guy here?
- Yes. sir. he's my--
[all gasp]
That guy?
[breathing heavily]
Sir.
[Tony sobbing]
Just...
Just what?
- Just what? What?
- You know what? This...
- Just. please... Just--
- "Just. please..."
- Sir. please.
- Please. Sir.
- Yes. speak.
- Let us--
We're American journalists.
You told me that already.
Okay. we--
We work for Reuters.
Reuters doesn't sound American.
[stammers] Okay-- It's a news agency.
- I know what Reuters is.
- Sir. Okay.
- I'm just saying...
- Just saying. just what?
We're American. okay?
Okay.
What kind of American are you?
Central American. South American?
What?
Florida.
Florida?
Central?
[sniffles]
What about you? Where are you from?
Uh... [whimpering]
Tell him. Jessie.
Missouri.
Missouri?
The "Show-Me" state. right?
Yes.
Isn't that what they call it?
[Jessie] Yes.
Why do they call it the "Show-Me" state?
I don't know.
You don't know?
[chuckles]
It's American.
- It is American. hundred percent.
- Yes.
[Jessie sniffles]
What about you? Where are you from?
Colorado.
Colorado. Missouri.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's American.
[Jessie sobbing]
Who's this guy hiding over here?
Hey. Buddy.
[sobbing]
What's your deal? Where are you from?
- Huh?
- [sobbing]
Where are you from?
What? You can't speak? Are you mute?
- [sobbing]
- You can't speak English?
Yes. you can? Yes. you can't?
Okay.
[continues sobbing]
You open your mouth
and tell me where you're from.
Just make sure
it's clear fucking English. Okay?
[sobbing]
Where are you from?
I'm from... I'm from Hong Kong.
Oh. China?
[gunshot]
[grunts]
China.
- [Jessie crying]
- [Joel] Sir. just--
- [Jessie] No!
- [man 1] What? What?
- Just stop it. okay?
- Stop?
- No. no. no!
- Who the fuck...
- Stop it!
- ...do you think you are...
[indistinct screaming]
[brakes screech]
Get in the car! Get in the fucking car!
[sobs. grunts]
[gasps]
[unsettling music plays]
Go. go. go. go! Go!
- [car doors closing]
- [panting]
[car revving]
[Jessie screams]
Fuck.
[unsettling music building]
[coughs]
[retches]
We gotta stop.
What are you talking about?
I can't drive.
[Joel] We can't stop.
You gotta fucking drive.
- Joel.
- I can't.
He's been hit. He's bleeding.
No. no. no. no. no. no!
Fuck!
Fuck! Okay. get up. Get up.
- Let's go.
- [Sammy choking]
Come on. Let's go. Sammy.
[breathing heavily]
- Okay. Okay.
- Come on.
[Sammy panting]
[gurgling]
[Lee panting]
Fuck!
[panting]
['Breakers Roar"
by Sturgill Simpson playing]
["Breakers Roar" playing]
[inaudible]
[song fades]
[whooshing]
[indistinct shouting. chatter]
We just heard about Sammy.
And the other two guys.
Tony. Bohai. Their names.
Lee. I'm really sorry.
I know what he was to you.
It's so fucked up.
Oh. it's so fucked up.
Now you wait until you hear what these
two embattled motherfuckers have to say.
Joel. I'm just trying to talk to Lee
about Sammy.
I know. Yeah. I heard.
Your condolences means a lot.
Now just. just tell her.
We loved Sammy. everyone did.
[scoffs]
Thank you. Anya.
Fuck. The Western Forces
are moving to D.C.
Earlier today. the government.
military. basically surrendered.
Yeah. it's true.
D.C.'s only protection now...
few do-or-die soldiers.
handful of Secret Service.
WF's gonna roll right in.
So you and I. we're too late.
We missed the story.
And Sammy didn't even die
for anything good.
[helicopter hovering in distance]
[birds chirping]
[helicopter whirring in distance]
[Jessie] Where's Joel?
Processing.
Me too.
Hardly knew Sammy compared to you. but...
Yeah. you knew him.
The man you were with.
that's who he was.
It may sound fucked up.
but there are so many ways
that it could've ended for him.
And a lot of them were worse.
He didn't wanna quit.
These last few days... [sniffles]
I've never been scared like that before.
And I've never felt more alive.
[helicopter whirring in distance]
[helicopter hovering]
[indistinct shouting]
[soft music playing]
[inaudible]
[soft music continues]
- [man 1] Sniper!
- [man 2] Halt! We got a sniper!
[man 1] Man down!
[indistinct shouting]
Move. move! Move. move. move!
Take your positions! Move. move. move!
[gunfire continues]
- [man 1] Move! Come here!
- [man 2] Move. move. move!
[indistinct shouting]
Lee?
[panting]
Let's go!
[distant explosions]
- [gunfire continues]
- [indistinct radio chatter]
[indistinct radio chatter continues]
- [man 1] Go. go. go!
- [woman] Come on. Come on.
[man 2] We got her.
we got her. we got her.
Go. go. go. go. go! Go! Go!
Get to the back! In position now! Go! Go!
[Lee panting]
Fire!
- Go. go. go. go!
- [indistinct shouting]
For fuck's sake. stay down.
Friendly. friendly. friendly.
- Lock it down.
- Right now!
We're here to help. What do you need?
[woman] We got two over there
and two in the tower.
I can send a main round
right through that tower.
- Yeah. just fuckin' do it. do it.
- Okay.
Get back. On me. Drop that bitch.
- Stand back!
Ladies. get your head down! Tuck in!
Gun tower. the north side.
seventeen street. Mark my Tracer.
[indistinct shouting]
- Move. move. move!
- Come on. let's go!
- Move it!
- Come on! Come on!
Go. go. go!
[woman] Let's just go. let's go. let's go!
Go. go. go. go!
[grunting]
[indistinct shouting]
[camera shutter clicking]
Lee. we gotta move. okay?
We have to move.
Let's go. Let's go. Now!
[woman] Get down. get down. get down!
[Lee whimpering]
Hit the wall again.
Push it back. push it back.
- Get back!
- Get at the back!
- Stay clear!
- Hey!
[man 2] Move it! Move it!
[man 3] On me. Let's move.
Move. move. move.
Move it!
- Jessie!
- [man] Move!
Get over here. now!
[woman] Cover the perimeter!
[man 4] Go. go. go!
[woman] Move. move. Tuck in. Tuck in.
Kill the mortar!
- Give me two!
- Two soldiers move in.
- Let's go!
- Let's go. Go. go. go!
Go. go. go. go. go!
- Go now. fast!
- Go. go. go!
You ready? On my count.
Oh. my God. We're so fucking close.
Come on. let's go. Again.
Western Forces have reached
the White House perimeter.
The president is now surrounded.
We've approached from Pennsylvania Avenue.
Fuck!
Just give me a minute.
We're gonna have to go again.
You get new shit?
Lincoln Memorial. You?
WF rappelling out of a chopper
onto the roof of the fucking Pentagon.
There's really only one shot though. huh?
You know he's in there?
[man] They got intel from the generals
that surrendered yesterday.
The president's
right in that fucking building.
Fuck.
What do you hear
they're gonna do with him?
Kill. No capture.
Whoever gets a fucking gun
to his head first.
Hey. Lee!
Don't beat me to the money shot. huh?
Got the beast.
Two Suburbans right outside.
The president's on the move.
Fuck. yeah. He's bustin' out.
- [cars revving]
- [tires screeching]
[gunfire continues]
[tires screeching]
Vehicle coming through!
Beast. beast. beast!
[man] Another one!
[reporter] His vehicle has been stopped
by Western Forces
as it attempted to escape.
He's not in there.
What? What?
[breathing heavily]
- Okay. Let's go.
- But...
- Let's go. Jessie.
- What do you mean? What?
- [Joel] Come on! Now!
- What?
- On me. On me.
- The reporter is movin' out.
Don't shoot. don't shoot.
Please! Don't...
[distant explosions. gunfire]
This place is empty.
[panting]
Stay the fuck out of our way.
Follow me.
[gunfire]
[woman] Hold your fire.
I said hold your fire.
I'm alone.
Unarmed.
Standing in the middle
of the press briefing room.
[door opens]
Secret Service agent. Joy Butler.
- Drop it.
- [Joy] I'm unarmed. I'm here to talk.
- Take it.
- Flood it.
I'm here to negotiate
the surrender of the president.
[camera shutter clicks]
He's here.
You the WF?
Take a wild guess.
Can the president be entrusted
into your safe care?
Yes. ma'am.
We'll take real good care of him.
Just bring him out here.
We're not bringing him anywhere
until we have agreed terms.
We need a guarantee
of safe passage for the president.
And we need extraction
to a neutral territory.
We request Greenland or Alaska.
Nah. no terms. Bring him out here.
[man] We gotta move. Sergeant.
Ma'am. the President is willing--
Gunner! Point check! Move in!
- Come on. get back!
- Contact. one!
[gunfire continues]
Just go. Go!
[camera shutter clicking]
Out! Reloading!
[camera shutter clicks]
[indistinct shouting]
- Get back!
I got him!
- Give it up!
- [indistinct shouting]
Ready to crash! Ready to crash!
Check!
I'm out. Reloading. reloading.
- Prep. black.
- [bullet ricochets]
- Up!
- Yes. sirl
Crash it!
Go!
Go! Go!
Move it.
Wait! Wait!
Move it!
Chief. clear left!
Roger that!
Bust across! Bust across!
Check.
Forward.
Gunner. I'm moving across.
I need you to lead us in fire.
Sergeant. you're going left.
Follow me. I'm going left.
You move when I move.
Copy you!
- You guys ready to move?
- Ready. check!
- Move!
- Move it! Move!
Let's go!
[all shouting indistinctly]
[body thuds]
You good?
- Stay down.
- [whirs]
- Deacon flare!
- Move! You gotta move on!
Move. move. go!
- Move out!
- Move in.
Ready.
Break out. break out. break out.
[woman] Tuck in. tuck in. tuck in.
- I'm out. I'm out. Reloading.
- Changing.
[gunshots]
Prepping crash!
[camera shutter clicking]
- [unsettling music playing]
- [panting]
[inaudible]
[unsettling music playing]
- [Joel] Wait!
- [rifle cocks]
Wait!
[breathing shakily]
I need a quote.
[breathing heavily]
Don't let... Don't let them kill me.
[panting]
Yeah.
that'll do.
["Dream Baby Dream" by Suicide playing]
["Dream Baby Dream" playing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[whirs. clicks]
[song cross-fades]
[soft music playing]
[music ends]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm